{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_5JX62F",
                "player_16_5JX62F",
                "player_3_5JX62F",
                "player_12_5JX62F"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                16,
                3,
                12
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "pick_up",
                "crouch",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man with dark skin, wearing a black fedora, black turtleneck, black pants, and black shoes.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    642.447,
                    9281.684,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    28.497206397582147,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    938.532,
                    9669.301,
                    1248.151,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    880.074,
                    9306.789,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    75.6424773150346,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    812.392,
                    8981.09,
                    1248.15,
                    0,
                    63.09038584027266,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            92.965,
            9662.22,
            1258.25
        ],
        "sample_radius": 1190.7650050486236
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            702.078,
            8647.76,
            1248.15,
            0,
            80.03672625905548,
            0
        ],
        [
            384.723,
            9161.144,
            1248.15,
            0,
            18.91235096994557,
            0
        ],
        [
            1136.096,
            9965.848,
            1248.151,
            0,
            -115.83878642520591,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_fedora_hat or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_fedora_hat",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_fedora_hat, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_fedora_hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_fedora_hat"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What is the total number of males present in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many individuals are depicted with black skin?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many people in the scene are lying down on the ground?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many females are visible in the entire scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many people are carrying a heavy sack?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a navy blue polo shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a black fedora?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walking",
                    "B. holding a bag",
                    "C. waving",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding a bag"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman with dark hair in a bun?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. sit",
                    "D. run"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing a gray suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. lie down",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V-top relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in fedora hat?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. Behind"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the woman in deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in fedora hat relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}